<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My News Site</title>
    <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My News Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ethnic Cleansing of Albanians in Yugoslavia: An Analysis of Vaso Čubrilović’s Plan and the Yugoslavia–Turkey Agreement (1937–1953)</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/ethnic-cleansing-of-albanians-in-yugoslavia-an-analysis-of-vaso-%C4%8Dubrilovi%C4%87s-plan-and-the-yugoslaviaturkey-agreement-19371953-332399230/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/ethnic-cleansing-of-albanians-in-yugoslavia-an-analysis-of-vaso-%C4%8Dubrilovi%C4%87s-plan-and-the-yugoslaviaturkey-agreement-19371953-332399230/</guid>
      <description>Author: Flamur Buçpapaj
Scientific Study
Field: Political Science / History / International Law
This study examines the Yugoslav state’s efforts to ethnically cleanse Muslim Albanians during the interwar period and after World War II. Focusing on Vaso Čubrilović’s memorandum Iseljavanje Arnauta (“Expulsion of the Albanians,” 1937) and the Yugoslavia–Turkey Agreement (1938), the study argues that ethnic cleansing was not merely nationalist rhetoric but a systematic state policy designed and implemented to alter the ethnic composition of Kosovo and other Albanian regions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Message To Erdogan? PM Modi Clicked With Cyprus President, Turkish-Controlled North In Backdrop</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/message-to-erdogan-pm-modi-clicked-with-cyprus-president-turkishcontrolled-north-in-backdrop-331898484/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/message-to-erdogan-pm-modi-clicked-with-cyprus-president-turkishcontrolled-north-in-backdrop-331898484/</guid>
      <description>India strongly backed Cyprus’s “independence, sovereignty, and territorial integrity” during Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s visit on Monday — a move widely seen as a clear message to Turkey, which claims part of the island nation. PM Modi toured the capital city of Nicosia, which too remains divided, and was photographed against the backdrop of the flag of the Turkish-controlled north — a moment analysts interpreted as a subtle but firm geopolitical signal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Airlines and TAP Air Portugal Expand Cooperation Scope</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-airlines-and-tap-air-portugal-expand-cooperation-scope-331565512/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-airlines-and-tap-air-portugal-expand-cooperation-scope-331565512/</guid>
      <description>(MENAFN- Ogilvy) Turkish Airlines, the airline that flies to more countries than any other in the world, and TAP Air Portugal, the flag carrier of Portugal and the leading European airline flying to Brazil, are expanding their existing codeshare partnership.
As part of the recently expanded agreement announced during the IATA Annual General Meeting held in New Delhi, both carriers will now provide their guests with a broader range of seamless travel options beyond their current global networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel &amp;#8216;greatest threat&amp;#8217; to region’s stability, Turkish president tells Saudi crown prince</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/israel-8216greatest-threat8217-to-regions-stability-turkish-president-tells-saudi-crown-prince-331442790/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/israel-8216greatest-threat8217-to-regions-stability-turkish-president-tells-saudi-crown-prince-331442790/</guid>
      <description>Israel is the “greatest threat” to the region’s stability and security, said Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Saturday in a phone call with Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, Anadolu reports.
President Erdogan said “Israel, under the Netanyahu administration, poses the greatest threat to the region’s stability and security, and this has been reaffirmed through its recent attack on Iran,” Turkiye’s Communications Directorate said in a statement on X.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mum-of-four&#39;s partner was escorted off holiday flight for being drunk, she never saw him again</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/mumoffours-partner-was-escorted-off-holiday-flight-for-being-drunk-she-never-saw-him-again-331224478/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/mumoffours-partner-was-escorted-off-holiday-flight-for-being-drunk-she-never-saw-him-again-331224478/</guid>
      <description>The partner of a man who died on their family holiday to Turkey has said she is only existing now for the sake of their kids, and that his death has traumatised her for life. Ben Crook, 32, from Caerphilly , died after suffering a fall on his arrival in Antalya in September last year. An inquest on Tuesday, June 10, at Gwent Coroner&amp;rsquo;s Court heard that Ben had been escorted off the plane by Turkish police upon landing, after being drunk and disorderly during the flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Latest: Iran fires more missiles at Israel after Israeli military continues strikes</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/the-latest-iran-fires-more-missiles-at-israel-after-israeli-military-continues-strikes-331588006/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/the-latest-iran-fires-more-missiles-at-israel-after-israeli-military-continues-strikes-331588006/</guid>
      <description>Iran launched a second round of missiles against Israel late Saturday as Israel’s military kept up attacks in Iran following earlier strikes that targeted nuclear and military sites. They also killed key leaders in the country’s governing theocracy.
Israel said hundreds of airstrikes over the past two days killed nine senior scientists and experts involved in Iran’s nuclear program, in addition to several top generals. Iran’s U.N. ambassador said 78 people were killed and more than 320 wounded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welsh mum-of-four&#39;s partner was escorted off holiday flight for being drunk, she never saw him again</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/welsh-mumoffours-partner-was-escorted-off-holiday-flight-for-being-drunk-she-never-saw-him-again-331314166/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/welsh-mumoffours-partner-was-escorted-off-holiday-flight-for-being-drunk-she-never-saw-him-again-331314166/</guid>
      <description>The partner of a man who died on their family holiday to Turkey has said she is only existing now for the sake of their kids, and that his death has traumatised her for life.
Ben Crook, 32, from Caerphilly, died after suffering a fall on his arrival in Antalya in September last year. An inquest on Tuesday, June 10, at Gwent Coroner&amp;rsquo;s Court heard that Ben had been escorted off the plane by Turkish police upon landing, after being drunk and disorderly during the flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Family star Ariel Winter, 27, talks &#39;scary&#39; move of posing as a 12-year-old decoy to nab a sexual predator</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/modern-family-star-ariel-winter-27-talks-scary-move-of-posing-as-a-12yearold-decoy-to-nab-a-sexual-predator-331205216/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/modern-family-star-ariel-winter-27-talks-scary-move-of-posing-as-a-12yearold-decoy-to-nab-a-sexual-predator-331205216/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday
Kim Kardashian
Victoria Beckham
Harry Styles
Amanda Holden
Britain&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent
Privacy Policy
Friday, Jun 13th 2025
5-Day Forecast
Advertisement
Emotional David Beckham FINALLY gets knighthood after years of being snubbed and describes it as &amp;lsquo;truly humbling&amp;rsquo; as he joins Luke Littler and Claudia Winkleman on King&amp;rsquo;s Birthday Honours list
Expert&amp;rsquo;s theory on terrifyingly simple mistake he thinks Air India co-pilot made that caused crash and killed 265</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Latest: Israel attacks Iran, killing at least 2 military officers</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/the-latest-israel-attacks-iran-killing-at-least-2-military-officers-331016118/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/the-latest-israel-attacks-iran-killing-at-least-2-military-officers-331016118/</guid>
      <description>By The Associated Press
Israel launched a wave of strikes across Iran on Friday that targeted its nuclear program and military sites, killing at least two top military officers and raising the prospect of an all-out war between the two bitter Middle East adversaries.
It appeared to be the most significant attack Iran has faced since its 1980s war with Iraq.
Iran quickly retaliated, sending a swarm of drones at Israel as Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei warned of “severe punishment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan Condemns Israel’s Attacks on Iran, Calling for International Action</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-president-recep-tayyip-erdogan-condemns-israels-attacks-on-iran-calling-for-international-action-331199282/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-president-recep-tayyip-erdogan-condemns-israels-attacks-on-iran-calling-for-international-action-331199282/</guid>
      <description>Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan condemns Israel’s attacks on Iran, calling for international action:
Erdogan says Netanyahu government’s &amp;lsquo;reckless, lawless and aggressive actions&amp;rsquo; risk plunging Middle East and world into disaster
Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan condemned Israel’s attack against Iran on Friday, calling it a “blatant provocation” that disregards international law and threatens regional and global stability.
Israel launched a large-scale attack early Friday, deploying around 200 aircraft to target Iran’s nuclear program and long-range missile capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emirhan Demircan &#39;rejects&#39; Ranger transfer offer as Bayern Munich starlet links up with pricey Celtic flop instead</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/emirhan-demircan-rejects-ranger-transfer-offer-as-bayern-munich-starlet-links-up-with-pricey-celtic-flop-instead-330812380/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/emirhan-demircan-rejects-ranger-transfer-offer-as-bayern-munich-starlet-links-up-with-pricey-celtic-flop-instead-330812380/</guid>
      <description>Emirhan Demircan has knocked back an offer from Rangers to join them this summer, according to a report. The former Bayern Munich youngster has left the Allianz Arena as a free agent after his contract expired. Demircan progressed through the ranks in Bavaria after joining from city rivals 1860 Munich as a teenager. But now he&amp;rsquo;s moved on, although he won&amp;rsquo;t be joining the American revolution at Ibrox . Fabrizio Romano, amongst others, claims that Gers were one of the clubs to put an offer to Demircan along with Turkish giants Besiktas and Bundesliga outfit Hoffenheim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leroy Sane officially joins Galatasaray from Bayern: Decoding his stats</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/leroy-sane-officially-joins-galatasaray-from-bayern-decoding-his-stats-330831416/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/leroy-sane-officially-joins-galatasaray-from-bayern-decoding-his-stats-330831416/</guid>
      <description>Bayern Munich winger Leroy Sane has completed a move to Turkish champions Galatasaray. The 29-year-old player had arrived in Istanbul on Thursday to finalize a contract with the Super Lig champions. As per Fabrizio Romano, he has now officially joined Galatasaray on a three-year contract. Earlier, the Turkish club shared photos on social media showing Sane wearing a Galatasaray scarf upon his arrival at Ataturk Airport, confirming that they have started transfer talks with him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rangers transfer news as big spenders join Matija Frigan chase and Vaclav Cerny loan terms ‘revealed’</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/rangers-transfer-news-as-big-spenders-join-matija-frigan-chase-and-vaclav-cerny-loan-terms-revealed-330601906/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/rangers-transfer-news-as-big-spenders-join-matija-frigan-chase-and-vaclav-cerny-loan-terms-revealed-330601906/</guid>
      <description>Interest in Rangers target Matija Frigan is heating up - with the Westerlo frontman now linked with a reunion with one of his former managers who has taken up the reins at an English Championship club. Record Sport understands that the Croatian striker is a summer target for new Gers sporting director Kevin Thelwell , who is keen to make his mark at Ibrox. Frigan joined Westerlo from Rijeka in 2023 and has scored 19 goals across his two seasons so far in Belgum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lantos Human Rights Commission Hearing Focuses on Human Rights Abuses in Turkey</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/tom-lantos-human-rights-commission-hearing-focuses-on-human-rights-abuses-in-turkey-330203470/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/tom-lantos-human-rights-commission-hearing-focuses-on-human-rights-abuses-in-turkey-330203470/</guid>
      <description>Washington, D.C. – Today’s Tom Lantos Human Rights Commission hearing, “Human Rights in Turkey Today,” addressed the human rights situation in Turkey and featured panelists Enes Kanter Freedom, human rights activist and former NBA player, Alp Aslandogan, Executive Director of Alliance For Shared Values, and Dr. Michael Rubin, Senior Fellow at the American Enterprise Institute, who discussed the government of Turkey’s human rights abuses, U.S. response, and recommendations for Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish and Kurdish groups in UK complain of intimidation by Turkey</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-and-kurdish-groups-in-uk-complain-of-intimidation-by-turkey-330624336/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-and-kurdish-groups-in-uk-complain-of-intimidation-by-turkey-330624336/</guid>
      <description>Members of the Turkish and Kurdish community in the UK have accused the Turkish government of intimidating and interrogating them for holding arts and cultural events in London parks.
They claim that about 150 people who have participated in activities organised by Gik-Der – Refugee Workers’ Cultural Organisation have been detained by Turkish authorities when visiting Turkey and questioned about their involvement with the organisation.
They say they have been accused of having links to an illegal organisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple supercharges its tools and technologies for developers</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/apple-supercharges-its-tools-and-technologies-for-developers-329767914/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/apple-supercharges-its-tools-and-technologies-for-developers-329767914/</guid>
      <description>PRESS RELEASE
June 9, 2025
Apple supercharges its tools and technologies for developers to foster creativity, innovation, and design
Access to the on-device Apple Intelligence model, large language model integration in Xcode, and an elegant new software design across Apple platforms give developers everything they need to build beautiful modern apps with speed and confidence
CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA Apple today announced new technologies and enhancements to its developer tools to help developers create more beautiful, intelligent, and engaging app experiences across Apple platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global condemnations pour in after Israeli attack on aid ship</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/global-condemnations-pour-in-after-israeli-attack-on-aid-ship-329616828/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/global-condemnations-pour-in-after-israeli-attack-on-aid-ship-329616828/</guid>
      <description>Israeli forces attacked Madleen Gaza-bound aid ship and abducted the crew as the vessel approached the coastal waters of the besieged Palestinian territory early on Monday, Press TV reported.
Climate activist Greta Thunberg was among 12 international campaigners aboard the Madleen. “Game of Thrones” actor Liam Cunningham and Rima Hassan, a French member of the European Parliament of Palestinian descent, were also onboard.
Turkey slams seizure as violation of international law</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey slams Israel for intercepting Gaza-bound aid boat</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkey-slams-israel-for-intercepting-gazabound-aid-boat-329637374/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkey-slams-israel-for-intercepting-gazabound-aid-boat-329637374/</guid>
      <description>ISTANBUL: Turkey slammed Israel for intercepting a Gaza-bound boat carrying activists including Swedish campaigner Greta Thunberg early on Monday, describing it as a “heinous attack”.
The Madleen left Italy on June 1 to raise awareness over food shortages in Gaza, which the United Nations has described as the “hungriest place on Earth”, with the entire population at risk of famine.
“The intervention by Israeli forces on the ‘Madleen’ ship.. while sailing in international waters is a clear violation of international law,” Turkey said, calling it as a “heinous attack” by the government of Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Liverpool and Arsenal star Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain &#39;offered&#39; surprise Championship deal</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/exliverpool-and-arsenal-star-alex-oxladechamberlain-offered-surprise-championship-deal-329122672/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/exliverpool-and-arsenal-star-alex-oxladechamberlain-offered-surprise-championship-deal-329122672/</guid>
      <description>Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain is being eyed by Leicester after Ole Gunnar Solskjaer made it clear that Besiktas want to sell him this summer. Oxlade-Chamberlain has just finished his second season with Besiktas and it seems he could be approaching the end of his time in Istanbul. The former Arsenal midfielder arrived in Turkey in the summer of 2023 after leaving Liverpool on a free transfer. He has endured a rollercoaster time with Besiktas, playing under nine different managers during his two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azerbaijani diaspora funds release of book on Armenian massacres in Türkiye&#39;s Igdir</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/azerbaijani-diaspora-funds-release-of-book-on-armenian-massacres-in-t%C3%BCrkiyes-igdir-328861246/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/azerbaijani-diaspora-funds-release-of-book-on-armenian-massacres-in-t%C3%BCrkiyes-igdir-328861246/</guid>
      <description>BAKU, Azerbaijan, June 6. The book \&amp;ldquo;Armenian Massacre in Igdir through the Eyes of Witnesses\&amp;rdquo; by Ziya Zakir Acar, head of the Association for the Survival and Support of the Igdir-Azerbaijani Language, History and Culture Community and the Igdir Azerbaijani House, has been published in Türkiye, the Azerbaijani State Committee on Work with Diaspora said, Trend reports.
The author of the foreword to the book, published with the committee&amp;rsquo;s financial support, is its first deputy chairman Valeh</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOM Cruise Missile: Türkiye Successfully Conducts First Test of SOM Cruise Missile Featuring New Homegrown Turbojet Engine</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/som-cruise-missile-t%C3%BCrkiye-successfully-conducts-first-test-of-som-cruise-missile-featuring-new-homegrown-turbojet-engine-328826332/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/som-cruise-missile-t%C3%BCrkiye-successfully-conducts-first-test-of-som-cruise-missile-featuring-new-homegrown-turbojet-engine-328826332/</guid>
      <description>On June 6, 2025, Türkiye marked a critical milestone in its ongoing pursuit of defense self-sufficiency and technological autonomy. In a significant development for the Turkish defense sector, Roketsan’s Stand-Off Missile (SOM) program achieved a successful test firing with the domestically developed KTJ-3200 turbojet engine. The successful demonstration of this engine marks the full localization of the missile’s propulsion system, eliminating one of the last remaining foreign dependencies in Türkiye’s indigenous cruise missile program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey president Erdogan issues shocking order, asks Turkish people to give birth to…</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkey-president-erdogan-issues-shocking-order-asks-turkish-people-to-give-birth-to-328936394/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkey-president-erdogan-issues-shocking-order-asks-turkish-people-to-give-birth-to-328936394/</guid>
      <description>After the “Boycott Turkey” campaign Erdogan is now grappling with a new crisis. The population of Turkey is consistently decreasing and the Turkish womens low birth rate has emerged as a huge concern for President Recep Tayyip Erdogan. Declining birth rates are now being perceived as a threat larger than war. To address this the Turkish government has launched several measures to promote childbirth and has announced 2025 as the Year of the Family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victor Osimhen transfer twist as £59m decision made on Man Utd target</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/victor-osimhen-transfer-twist-as-59m-decision-made-on-man-utd-target-328623414/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/victor-osimhen-transfer-twist-as-59m-decision-made-on-man-utd-target-328623414/</guid>
      <description>Victor Osimhen has rejected a move to Al-Hilal in a potential boost to Manchester United&amp;rsquo;s hopes of signing the striker. Osimhen spent the season on loan at Galatasaray, firing them to the Turkish Super Lig and Turkish Cup double. He also previously starred for Napoli as they won the Serie A title back in 2023. But his career in Naples is over, with the Italian side keen to sell him this summer as he enters the final year of his contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Airlines and TAP Air Portugal Expand Codeshare Partnership</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-airlines-and-tap-air-portugal-expand-codeshare-partnership-328100348/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-airlines-and-tap-air-portugal-expand-codeshare-partnership-328100348/</guid>
      <description>Turkish Airlines and TAP Air Portugal, have announced an expansion to their existing codeshare partnership.
As part of the recently expanded agreement announced during the IATA Annual General Meeting held in New Delhi, both carriers will now provide their guests with a broader range of seamless travel options beyond their current global networks.
Brazil, Morocco, Qatar, and Mauritius are new and exciting destinations entering the scope of co-operation. Additionally, Dalaman and Bodrum, Türkiye’s prominent summer destinations, have also been added to the agreement, further augmenting travel options between Türkiye and Portugal, enhancing access to sought-after leisure destinations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holy Quran desecrated after theft from mosque in France: police</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/holy-quran-desecrated-after-theft-from-mosque-in-france-police-327727926/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/holy-quran-desecrated-after-theft-from-mosque-in-france-police-327727926/</guid>
      <description>A person stole a Holy Quran from a mosque near the French city of Lyon and set it on fire at the weekend, religious leaders and a police source said Tuesday.
On the night of Sunday to Monday, “an individual with an uncovered face entered the prayer room, grabbed a copy of the Holy Quran, set it on fire then dropped it outside the building before fleeing,” the council of mosques in the Rhone region said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new book recounts the formation of the Berlin Indian Independence Committee in 1914</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/a-new-book-recounts-the-formation-of-the-berlin-indian-independence-committee-in-1914-327160558/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/a-new-book-recounts-the-formation-of-the-berlin-indian-independence-committee-in-1914-327160558/</guid>
      <description>The Germans exhibited no particular interest in India before 1886. That year, they established consular relations with India by opening their first-ever embassy in Calcutta (the capital of British India then). Later, they sent only their best officers, adept at foreign dealings, to take care of affairs with India. They were in a strong position in Europe while Britain stood isolated despite its conquests, guarding its own, lacking the trust of its peers, amongst whom they failed to generate neither faith nor friendship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado has now recorded 10 measles cases this year as airport outbreak grows</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/colorado-has-now-recorded-10-measles-cases-this-year-as-airport-outbreak-grows-327400386/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/colorado-has-now-recorded-10-measles-cases-this-year-as-airport-outbreak-grows-327400386/</guid>
      <description>Colorado has now confirmed 10 measles cases this year, after three more people got sick in the outbreak tied to Denver International Airport.
Two of the new cases were unvaccinated adults living in El Paso County who passed through the airport at about the same time on May 14. The third was a vaccinated Arapahoe County resident who was a passenger on Turkish Airlines flight 201, which landed at DIA on May 13 and carried a contagious passenger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Convicted Over Koran-Burning in London Says Ruling Is Assault on Free Speech</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/man-convicted-over-koranburning-in-london-says-ruling-is-assault-on-free-speech-327375118/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/man-convicted-over-koranburning-in-london-says-ruling-is-assault-on-free-speech-327375118/</guid>
      <description>A man who burned a Koran outside the Turkish consulate in London has branded his prosecution “an assault on free speech” as campaigners argued the ruling “signals a concerning capitulation to Islamic blasphemy codes.”
Hamit Coskun was found guilty on Monday of a religiously aggravated public order offence, having shouted “[Expletive] Islam,” “Islam is religion of terrorism,” and “Koran is burning” while holding the flaming religious text aloft earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man convicted over Koran-burning in London says ruling is assault on free speech</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/man-convicted-over-koranburning-in-london-says-ruling-is-assault-on-free-speech-327350956/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/man-convicted-over-koranburning-in-london-says-ruling-is-assault-on-free-speech-327350956/</guid>
      <description>A man who burned a Koran outside the Turkish consulate in London has branded his prosecution “an assault on free speech” as campaigners argued the ruling “signals a concerning capitulation to Islamic blasphemy codes”.
Hamit Coskun was found guilty on Monday of a religiously aggravated public order offence, having shouted “f*** Islam”, “Islam is religion of terrorism” and “Koran is burning” while holding the flaming religious text aloft earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Ilham Aliyev received Turkish Minister of Energy and Natural Resources</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/president-ilham-aliyev-received-turkish-minister-of-energy-and-natural-resources-327236190/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/president-ilham-aliyev-received-turkish-minister-of-energy-and-natural-resources-327236190/</guid>
      <description>02.06.202512:48
новости на русском
azərbaycan dilində
Latest News
Arts &amp;amp; Entertainment
Azernews.az
Weird / Interesting
Photo Galleries
Voice of Diaspora
Your Corner
TODAY.AZ / Politics
President Ilham Aliyev received Turkish Minister of Energy and Natural Resources
02 June 2025 [12:03] - TODAY.AZ
President of the Republic of Azerbaijan Ilham Aliyev received Alparslan Bayraktar, Minister of Energy and Natural Resources of the Republic of Türkiye, on June 2.
URL: http://www.today.az/news/politics/259589.html
Print version</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia Ukraine War: Second Round of Russia-Ukraine Peace Talks in Istanbul Ends Abruptly Amid Escalating Tensions</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/russia-ukraine-war-second-round-of-russiaukraine-peace-talks-in-istanbul-ends-abruptly-amid-escalating-tensions-327396138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/russia-ukraine-war-second-round-of-russiaukraine-peace-talks-in-istanbul-ends-abruptly-amid-escalating-tensions-327396138/</guid>
      <description>The second round of peace negotiations between Russia and Ukraine concluded abruptly in Istanbul on June 2, 2025, lasting barely an hour and yielding no significant progress. The talks, held at the historic Ciragan Palace, were overshadowed by recent escalations, including a substantial Ukrainian drone strike on Russian military assets. Second Round of Russia-Ukraine Peace Talks in Istanbul Ends Abruptly Amid Escalating Tensions Turkish officials reported that the meeting commenced nearly two hours late without any official explanation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KHADIJA KHAN: I don&#39;t approve of burning books, but the man on trial for setting fire to a Koran has a right to protest, whatever Islamists and their apologists say</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/khadija-khan-i-dont-approve-of-burning-books-but-the-man-on-trial-for-setting-fire-to-a-koran-has-a-right-to-protest-whatever-islamists-and-their-apologists-say-327001462/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/khadija-khan-i-dont-approve-of-burning-books-but-the-man-on-trial-for-setting-fire-to-a-koran-has-a-right-to-protest-whatever-islamists-and-their-apologists-say-327001462/</guid>
      <description>Growing up in my native Pakistan, I came to the conclusion that Islam was discriminatory and misogynistic. It was a religion that had been weaponised to keep independent-thinking women like me, and anyone who opposes the fundamentalists, in their place by fear.
I&amp;rsquo;d watched, appalled, at news footage of people being lynched in the street or burned alive for raising the questions about Islam I had privately asked myself.
As Pakistan became more and more radicalised, this slowly became a routine occurrence rather than a one-off event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life inside one of Britain&#39;s most dangerous neighbourhoods: How locals in Hull suburb are fighting drugs crime crisis</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/life-inside-one-of-britains-most-dangerous-neighbourhoods-how-locals-in-hull-suburb-are-fighting-drugs-crime-crisis-327001452/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/life-inside-one-of-britains-most-dangerous-neighbourhoods-how-locals-in-hull-suburb-are-fighting-drugs-crime-crisis-327001452/</guid>
      <description>Life inside one of Britain&amp;rsquo;s most dangerous neighbourhoods: How locals in Hull suburb are fighting drugs crime crisis
Do YOU have a story? Email: john.james@mailonline.co.uk
By JOHN SIDDLE and JOHN JAMES
Published: 11:22 BST, 1 June 2025 | Updated: 11:46 BST, 1 June 2025
IT was once the lifeblood of Hull&amp;rsquo;s fishing industry, home to proud dockers and hard-working trawlermen.
But today, Hessle Road stands as a microcosm of decay, despair, and lawlessness in modern Britain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;They treated us like animals!&#39;  Mother whose dream holiday to Turkey was destroyed when her son was rushed into &#39;mortuary&#39;-esque hospital with &#39;excruciating stomach pain&#39; reveals worst things about emergency care abroad</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/they-treated-us-like-animals-mother-whose-dream-holiday-to-turkey-was-destroyed-when-her-son-was-rushed-into-mortuaryesque-hospital-with-excruciating-stomach-pain-reveals-worst-things-about-emergency-care-abroad-326870680/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/they-treated-us-like-animals-mother-whose-dream-holiday-to-turkey-was-destroyed-when-her-son-was-rushed-into-mortuaryesque-hospital-with-excruciating-stomach-pain-reveals-worst-things-about-emergency-care-abroad-326870680/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday
Latest Headlines
University Guide
Meghan Markle
Prince Harry
King Charles III
Privacy Policy
Saturday, May 31st 2025
5-Day Forecast
Advertisement
Doctor WHO? Billie Piper makes sensational return to BBC sci-fi show after twelve years replacing Ncuti Gatwa as THE Doctor
British father &amp;lsquo;caught spying for China&amp;rsquo; in FBI sting: Businessman, 63, who referred to Chinese leader Xi Jinping as &amp;lsquo;the Boss&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;attempted to smuggle arms into Beijing&amp;rsquo; facing 40 years in US jail</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ultra woke remote Highlands towns that want more migrants to move in... despite fighting a housing crisis</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/the-ultra-woke-remote-highlands-towns-that-want-more-migrants-to-move-in-despite-fighting-a-housing-crisis-326783154/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/the-ultra-woke-remote-highlands-towns-that-want-more-migrants-to-move-in-despite-fighting-a-housing-crisis-326783154/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday
Latest Headlines
University Guide
Meghan Markle
Prince Harry
King Charles III
Privacy Policy
Saturday, May 31st 2025
5-Day Forecast
Advertisement
Truth behind Hannah Spearritt&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;off-grid&amp;rsquo;, prepper life in Costa Rica, her VERY environmentally unfriendly car and her unlikely shopping habits
Valerie Mahaffey dead aged 71: Desperate Housewives and Young Sheldon star dies as tributes pour in
Is your underwear giving you CANCER? How new &amp;lsquo;breathable&amp;rsquo; versions can contain a host of deadly chemicals&amp;hellip; and the worst offender is this item EVERY woman uses&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish preacher urges preserving and exposing anti-humanity crimes in Azerbaijan&#39;s Shusha</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-preacher-urges-preserving-and-exposing-antihumanity-crimes-in-azerbaijans-shusha-326718268/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-preacher-urges-preserving-and-exposing-antihumanity-crimes-in-azerbaijans-shusha-326718268/</guid>
      <description>SHUSHA, Azerbaijan, May 31. Traces of crimes against humanity committed in the city of Shusha must be preserved and presented to the world community, a Turkish cleric Ahmet Erdem told Trend.
\&amp;ldquo;I came from the Turkish city of Kars, but this is my native land. My paternal grandfather was from the city of Shusha, and my maternal grandfather was from Ganja. They left for Türkiye during the Armenian oppression that took place here in 1918.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A coalition of conscience must rise to stop Israel’s genocidal war on Gaza</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/a-coalition-of-conscience-must-rise-to-stop-israels-genocidal-war-on-gaza-326535036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/a-coalition-of-conscience-must-rise-to-stop-israels-genocidal-war-on-gaza-326535036/</guid>
      <description>During the darkest days of World War II, Anne Frank and her family hid in a secret attic in Amsterdam to escape the horrors of Nazi persecution. Her posthumously published diary offered the world a haunting glimpse into the fear and trauma endured by Jewish families at the time.
Today, a tragically familiar story is unfolding in Palestine. This time, it is children like Anne Frank – tens of thousands of them – facing death by starvation and relentless bombardment by the Israeli government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Colorado measles case tied to Turkish Airlines flight into DIA</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/another-colorado-measles-case-tied-to-turkish-airlines-flight-into-dia-326292176/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/another-colorado-measles-case-tied-to-turkish-airlines-flight-into-dia-326292176/</guid>
      <description>A second Arapahoe County resident who was likely exposed to measles on a flight that landed at Denver International Airport has tested positive for the disease, Colorado public health officials said Thursday.
The state’s seventh measles case of the year was confirmed in a vaccinated adult who was a passenger on Turkish Airlines flight 201 from Istanbul, which landed at DIA on May 13.
An out-of-state passenger on the flight had measles and was at the airport, a hotel shuttle and a nearby Quality Inn and Suites on May 13 and 14, according to the Colorado Department of Public Health and Environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ireland eye Turkish delight as Nations League business end begins</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/ireland-eye-turkish-delight-as-nations-league-business-end-begins-326376276/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/ireland-eye-turkish-delight-as-nations-league-business-end-begins-326376276/</guid>
      <description>Advertisement
League of Ireland
Horse Racing
TV Listings
GAA Fixtures The Video Review
Sport meets news, current affairs, society &amp;amp; pop culture
Rugby Weekly Extra
Dive into all the news and analysis 3 times a week
The Football Family
Weekly insights from the week’s big talking points
Advertisement
More Stories
Ireland training at Esenler Erok Stadium yesterday.Ryan Byrne/INPHO
match preview
Ireland eye Turkish delight as Nations League business end begins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tarun Chugh attends Jain community event in Jabalpur #Gallery</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/tarun-chugh-attends-jain-community-event-in-jabalpur-gallery-326562092/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/tarun-chugh-attends-jain-community-event-in-jabalpur-gallery-326562092/</guid>
      <description>International
South Cinema
Social News XYZ Reviews
Movie Schedules
Movies News
Live Events
Motorsports
Other Sports
Science/Tech
Business Wire India
Environment
Home » Gallery » Other » Tarun Chugh attends Jain community event in Jabalpur #Gallery
Tarun Chugh attends Jain community event in Jabalpur #Gallery
Posted By: Social News XYZ May 30, 2025
Jabalpur: BJP National General Secretary Tarun Chugh participates in a Jain community programme at the Jain Mandir in Jabalpur on Friday, May 30, 2025.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The evolution of Islamic fashion in Trinidad and Tobago</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/the-evolution-of-islamic-fashion-in-trinidad-and-tobago-326468290/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/the-evolution-of-islamic-fashion-in-trinidad-and-tobago-326468290/</guid>
      <description>BAVINA SOOKDEO
On May 30, 1845, the Fatel Razack arrived in the Gulf of Paria carrying 225 indentured labourers from India. Until 1917, thousands more would make that same journey, laying the foundation for a vibrant Indo-TT community. Today, their cultural legacy lives on in the language, food, music, religion, and the fashion of this twin-island nation.
One devout Muslim, Farzaana Mohammed, spoke to Newsday about Islamic fashion in TT. Mohammed’s fashion story began with a deep personal love for style and self-expression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Shashi Tharoor&#39;s Comments Miss the Mark on Kerala&#39;s Aid to Turkey in 2023</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/why-shashi-tharoors-comments-miss-the-mark-on-keralas-aid-to-turkey-in-2023-326017542/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/why-shashi-tharoors-comments-miss-the-mark-on-keralas-aid-to-turkey-in-2023-326017542/</guid>
      <description>Thiruvananthapuram MP Shashi Tharoor&amp;rsquo;s recent comments—arguably ill-timed—suggested that perhaps the aid that the Kerala government sent to Turkey in 2023 was misplaced. He gives two reasons: firstly, Turkey is not a friendly nation, and secondly, the money could have been better utilised in the aftermath of a disaster in Kerala itself.The second reason can be safely ignored. We receive as much aid as we give out—there cannot be miserliness in humanitarian gestures, only moderation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At trilateral summit with Turkish and Azeri presidents, PM Shehbaz ‘rejects conflict’</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/at-trilateral-summit-with-turkish-and-azeri-presidents-pm-shehbaz-rejects-conflict-325733426/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/at-trilateral-summit-with-turkish-and-azeri-presidents-pm-shehbaz-rejects-conflict-325733426/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Shehbaz Sharif on Wednesday said he, along with the presidents of Turkiye and Azerbaijan, had gathered at a trilateral summit to “reject conflict”.
The prime minister participated in the Pakistan-Turkiye-Azerbaijan Trilateral Summit alongside presidents Recep Tayyip Erdogan and Ilham Aliyev. The meeting comes as the premier continued his tour to friendly countries to appreciate their support for Pakistan during the recent conflict with India.
Speaking at the summit, PM Shehbaz said: “The world we live in faces numerous grave challenges, including armed conflict, climate change, diseases and economic crises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Britain risks &#39;reintroducing a blasphemy law&#39; by prosecuting man, 50, who allegedly shouted &#39;f*** Islam&#39; as he burned Koran outside Turkish consulate, court hears</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/britain-risks-reintroducing-a-blasphemy-law-by-prosecuting-man-50-who-allegedly-shouted-f-islam-as-he-burned-koran-outside-turkish-consulate-court-hears-325767978/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/britain-risks-reintroducing-a-blasphemy-law-by-prosecuting-man-50-who-allegedly-shouted-f-islam-as-he-burned-koran-outside-turkish-consulate-court-hears-325767978/</guid>
      <description>The prosecution of a man who allegedly burned a Koran outside the Turkish consulate in London risks &amp;lsquo;reintroducing a blasphemy law&amp;rsquo; in the UK, a court heard today.
Hamit Coskun, 50, allegedly shouted &amp;lsquo;f*** Islam&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Islam is religion of terrorism&amp;rsquo; and Koran is burning&#39; as he held the flaming Muslim holy book aloft in Rutland Gardens, Knightsbridge, on February 13.
He pleaded not guilty to a religiously aggravated public order offence of using disorderly behaviour motivated by &amp;lsquo;hostility towards members of a religious group, namely followers of Islam&amp;rsquo; and also denied an alternative charge of using disorderly behaviour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burning of Koran outside Turkish consulate in Knightsbridge ‘posed a threat to public order’, trial hears</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/burning-of-koran-outside-turkish-consulate-in-knightsbridge-posed-a-threat-to-public-order-trial-hears-325737380/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/burning-of-koran-outside-turkish-consulate-in-knightsbridge-posed-a-threat-to-public-order-trial-hears-325737380/</guid>
      <description>The burning of a Koran outside the Turkish consulate in London went beyond a protest and posed a “threat to public order”, a trial heard.
Hamit Coskun, 50, allegedly shouted “f*** Islam”, “Islam is religion of terrorism” and “Koran is burning” as he held the flaming Islamic text aloft in Rutland Gardens, Knightsbridge, on February 13.
Coskun denies a religiously aggravated public order offence of using disorderly behaviour “within the hearing or sight of a person likely to be caused harassment, alarm or distress”, motivated by “hostility towards members of a religious group, namely followers of Islam”, contrary to the Crime and Disorder Act 1998 and the Public Order Act 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminalising Koran burning would be reintroducing blasphemy law, court told</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325772106/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325772106/</guid>
      <description>Prosecuting a man for burning the Koran is “tantamount to reintroducing a blasphemy law” in the UK, a trial heard.
Hamit Coskun, 50, shouted “f*** Islam”, “Islam is religion of terrorism” and “Koran is burning” as he held the flaming Islamic text aloft outside the Turkish consulate in Rutland Gardens, Knightsbridge, London, on February 13, Westminster Magistrates’ Court heard.
Coskun denies a religiously aggravated public order offence of using disorderly behaviour “within the hearing or sight of a person likely to be caused harassment, alarm or distress”, motivated by “hostility towards members of a religious group, namely followers of Islam”, contrary to the Crime and Disorder Act 1998 and the Public Order Act 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminalising Koran burning would be reintroducing blasphemy law, court told</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325801268/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325801268/</guid>
      <description>Prosecuting a man for burning the Koran is “tantamount to reintroducing a blasphemy law” in Great Britain, a trial heard.
Hamit Coskun, 50, shouted “f*** Islam”, “Islam is religion of terrorism” and “Koran is burning” as he held the flaming Islamic text aloft outside the Turkish consulate in Rutland Gardens, Knightsbridge, London, on February 13, Westminster Magistrates’ Court heard.
Coskun denies a religiously aggravated public order offence of using disorderly behaviour “within the hearing or sight of a person likely to be caused harassment, alarm or distress”, motivated by “hostility towards members of a religious group, namely followers of Islam”, contrary to the Crime and Disorder Act 1998 and the Public Order Act 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminalising Koran burning would be reintroducing blasphemy law, court told</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325829248/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325829248/</guid>
      <description>Prosecuting a man for burning the Koran is “tantamount to reintroducing a blasphemy law” in Great Britain, a trial heard.
Hamit Coskun, 50, shouted “f*** Islam”, “Islam is religion of terrorism” and “Koran is burning” as he held the flaming Islamic text aloft outside the Turkish consulate in Rutland Gardens, Knightsbridge, London, on February 13, Westminster Magistrates’ Court heard.
Coskun denies a religiously aggravated public order offence of using disorderly behaviour “within the hearing or sight of a person likely to be caused harassment, alarm or distress”, motivated by “hostility towards members of a religious group, namely followers of Islam”, contrary to the Crime and Disorder Act 1998 and the Public Order Act 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminalising Koran burning would be reintroducing blasphemy law, court told</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325848876/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325848876/</guid>
      <description>Prosecuting a man for burning the Koran is “tantamount to reintroducing a blasphemy law” in Great Britain, a trial heard.
Hamit Coskun, 50, shouted “f*** Islam”, “Islam is religion of terrorism” and “Koran is burning” as he held the flaming Islamic text aloft outside the Turkish consulate in Rutland Gardens, Knightsbridge, London, on February 13, Westminster Magistrates’ Court heard.
Coskun denies a religiously aggravated public order offence of using disorderly behaviour “within the hearing or sight of a person likely to be caused harassment, alarm or distress”, motivated by “hostility towards members of a religious group, namely followers of Islam”, contrary to the Crime and Disorder Act 1998 and the Public Order Act 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminalising Koran burning would be reintroducing blasphemy law, court told</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325885244/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/criminalising-koran-burning-would-be-reintroducing-blasphemy-law-court-told-325885244/</guid>
      <description>Prosecuting a man for burning the Koran is “tantamount to reintroducing a blasphemy law” in Great Britain, a trial heard.
Hamit Coskun, 50, shouted “f*** Islam”, “Islam is religion of terrorism” and “Koran is burning” as he held the flaming Islamic text aloft outside the Turkish consulate in Rutland Gardens, Knightsbridge, London, on February 13, Westminster Magistrates’ Court heard.
Coskun denies a religiously aggravated public order offence of using disorderly behaviour “within the hearing or sight of a person likely to be caused harassment, alarm or distress”, motivated by “hostility towards members of a religious group, namely followers of Islam”, contrary to the Crime and Disorder Act 1998 and the Public Order Act 1986.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish President Pledges to Continue to Tackle Regional Destabilization Attempts</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-president-pledges-to-continue-to-tackle-regional-destabilization-attempts-325872504/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-president-pledges-to-continue-to-tackle-regional-destabilization-attempts-325872504/</guid>
      <description>Baku, May 28 (QNA) - Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan said that his country is determined to continue to defend the rights of the babies and the innocent people killed in the Gaza Strip and to stand in the way of attempts to destabilize the region.
This came during his participation in a trilateral summit in Azerbaijan on Wednesday with Azerbaijani President Ilham Aliyev and Pakistani Prime Minister Shehbaz Sharif, in which Erdogan stressed that solidarity and joint action among their three countries is a necessity given regional developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World News | Kansas Community Holds Private Memorial for Israeli Embassy Staffer Killed in DC Ambush</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/world-news-kansas-community-holds-private-memorial-for-israeli-embassy-staffer-killed-in-dc-ambush-325490378/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/world-news-kansas-community-holds-private-memorial-for-israeli-embassy-staffer-killed-in-dc-ambush-325490378/</guid>
      <description>Washington, May 27 (AP) Family and friends of Sarah Milgrim, one of two Israeli Embassy staffers fatally shot last week in an apparently politically motivated ambush in Washington, DC, gathered for her funeral Tuesday in the Kansas community where she grew up. Milgrim, a 26-year-old from the Kansas City suburb of Prairie Village, Kansas, was leaving a reception for young diplomats at the Capital Jewish Museum alongside 30-year-old Yaron Lischinsky on May 21 when they were shot to death.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counterterrorism efforts, eliminating chemical weapons at center of US-Syria talks</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/counterterrorism-efforts-eliminating-chemical-weapons-at-center-of-ussyria-talks-325120790/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/counterterrorism-efforts-eliminating-chemical-weapons-at-center-of-ussyria-talks-325120790/</guid>
      <description>[Damascus] Syrian President Ahmed al-Sharaa and Foreign Minister Asaad al-Shaibani held a landmark meeting in Istanbul on Saturday with U.S. Ambassador to Turkey Tom Barrack, who was appointed a day earlier as US special envoy for Syria. They were joined by several senior Turkish officials. The diplomatic encounter marks the most significant engagement between Syria and the United States since the outbreak of the Syrian war in 2011. Observers described the summit as a decisive shift in Syrian-American relations and a potential prelude to reshaping regional power dynamics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only 900 speakers of the Sanna language remain. But Cyprus&#39; Maronites are mounting a comeback</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-but-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-325035048/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-but-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-325035048/</guid>
      <description>Ash dangled precariously from Iosif Skordis&#39; cigarette as he reminisced with fellow villagers in a language on the edge of extinction, one that partly traces its roots to the language Jesus Christ spoke. The 97-year-old Skordis is one of only 900 people who speak Cypriot Maronite Arabic, or Sanna. Today, his village of Kormakitis is the last bastion of a language once spoken by tens of thousands of people across dozens of villages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Türkiye&#39;s new war on faith: Erdoğan targets a “second FETÖ”</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/t%C3%BCrkiyes-new-war-on-faith-erdo%C4%9Fan-targets-a-second-fet%C3%B6-325107838/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/t%C3%BCrkiyes-new-war-on-faith-erdo%C4%9Fan-targets-a-second-fet%C3%B6-325107838/</guid>
      <description>Türkiye has entered a new phase in its long battle for control over the state—not against armed insurgents or opposition parties, but against a covert, deeply embedded religious network that has operated for decades behind a mask of piety. On the morning of May 15, 2025, the country woke up to headlines announcing sweeping arrests and raids. The target: the Süleymancı community—a religious order that has, until now, largely operated in the shadows, but whose reach, discipline, and political sophistication have long invited comparison to the once-powerful, now-outlawed FETÖ</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Austin mosques vandalized in 1 night, drawing concerns from Muslim community</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/3-austin-mosques-vandalized-in-1-night-drawing-concerns-from-muslim-community-324652004/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/3-austin-mosques-vandalized-in-1-night-drawing-concerns-from-muslim-community-324652004/</guid>
      <description>AUSTIN, Texas (WSVN) — The Muslim community in Austin, Texas, is on edge after three mosques were vandalized in one night. Now they’re asking police to step in.
Surveillance video captures a subject with his face covered as he spray-painted blue symbols that appear to be Stars of David at the Nueces Mosque in North Austin, Thursday evening.
“It’s so sad and very scary.” said Shaimaa Zayan, operations manager for Austin’s Council on American-Islamic Relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey’s Culinary Heritage Highlighted by Turkish Envoy in Nigeria</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkeys-culinary-heritage-highlighted-by-turkish-envoy-in-nigeria-325118590/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkeys-culinary-heritage-highlighted-by-turkish-envoy-in-nigeria-325118590/</guid>
      <description>Abuja: Turkish Ambassador to Nigeria, Mehmet Poroy, has highlighted Turkey’s rich culinary heritage, attributing it to the country’s historical enrichment by numerous civilizations. The ambassador shared these insights during an interactive dinner session with select diplomatic correspondents in Abuja.
According to News Agency of Nigeria, the dinner was part of the activities commemorating this year’s Turkish Cuisine Week, celebrated globally from May 21 to May 27. Ambassador Poroy emphasized that Turkey’s cuisine has evolved into a melting pot of diverse culinary traditions due to centuries of cultural interactions and migrations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Norton, 39, &#39;splits from model girlfriend Charlotte Rose Smith, 26, and signs up to celebrity dating app Raya&#39;</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/james-norton-39-splits-from-model-girlfriendcharlotte-rose-smith-26-and-signs-up-to-celebrity-dating-app-raya-324460252/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/james-norton-39-splits-from-model-girlfriendcharlotte-rose-smith-26-and-signs-up-to-celebrity-dating-app-raya-324460252/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday
Kim Kardashian
Victoria Beckham
Harry Styles
Amanda Holden
Britain&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent
Privacy Policy
Saturday, May 24th 2025
5-Day Forecast
Advertisement
Brit woman, 21, rotting in Dubai hell hole jail without &amp;lsquo;a shower for a month&amp;rsquo; after being arrested for drugs charges just weeks after arriving for new job
Shocking moment Labubu brawl breaks out with shoppers desperate for the must-have furry toys hurling punches at each other - as suppliers step in to BAN sales in the UK</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legendary voice actor with roles in Dragon Ball Z and Fantastic Mr Fox dies as anime community pays tribute</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/legendary-voice-actor-with-roles-in-dragon-ball-z-and-fantastic-mr-fox-dies-as-anime-community-pays-tribute-324411190/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/legendary-voice-actor-with-roles-in-dragon-ball-z-and-fantastic-mr-fox-dies-as-anime-community-pays-tribute-324411190/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday
Kim Kardashian
Victoria Beckham
Harry Styles
Amanda Holden
Britain&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent
Privacy Policy
Saturday, May 24th 2025
5-Day Forecast
Advertisement
Full timeline of the hunt for missing girl Pheobe Bishop, 17, whose disappearance has gripped Australia
Gran, 48, faces eviction from her three-bed council house after spending £30k on garden makeover without planning permission
James Martin rages at lawless London as yob smashes his car window after friends were mugged or had cars stolen in last two weeks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Keegan looks out of this world in a stylish white and black co-ord as she sips on cocktails in Cannes - two months after giving birth</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/michelle-keegan-looks-out-of-this-world-in-a-stylish-white-and-black-coord-as-she-sips-on-cocktails-in-cannes-two-months-after-giving-birth-324423454/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/michelle-keegan-looks-out-of-this-world-in-a-stylish-white-and-black-coord-as-she-sips-on-cocktails-in-cannes-two-months-after-giving-birth-324423454/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday
Kim Kardashian
Victoria Beckham
Harry Styles
Amanda Holden
Britain&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent
Privacy Policy
Saturday, May 24th 2025
5-Day Forecast
Advertisement
Full timeline of the hunt for missing girl Pheobe Bishop, 17, whose disappearance has gripped Australia
Gran, 48, faces eviction from her three-bed council house after spending £30k on garden makeover without planning permission
James Martin rages at lawless London as yob smashes his car window after friends were mugged or had cars stolen in last two weeks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only 900 speakers of the Sanna language remain. Now Cyprus&#39; Maronites are mounting a comeback</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-324330390/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-324330390/</guid>
      <description>Ash dangled precariously from Iosif Skordis&#39; cigarette as he reminisced with fellow villagers in a language on the edge of extinction, one that partly traces its roots to the language Jesus Christ once spoke.
The 97-year-old Skordis is one of only 900 people in the world who speak Cypriot Maronite Arabic, or Sanna. Today, his village of Kormakitis is the last bastion of a language once spoken by tens of thousands of people across dozens of villages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only 900 speakers of the Sanna language remain. Now Cyprus&#39; Maronites are mounting a comeback</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-324414152/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-324414152/</guid>
      <description>Ash dangled precariously from Iosif Skordis&#39; cigarette as he reminisced with fellow villagers in a language on the edge of extinction, one that partly traces its roots to the language Jesus Christ once spoke.
The 97-year-old Skordis is one of only 900 people in the world who speak Cypriot Maronite Arabic, or Sanna. Today, his village of Kormakitis is the last bastion of a language once spoken by tens of thousands of people across dozens of villages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only 900 speakers of the Sanna language remain. Now Cyprus&#39; Maronites are mounting a comeback</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-324441254/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-324441254/</guid>
      <description>KORMAKITIS, Cyprus (AP) — Ash dangled precariously from Iosif Skordis’ cigarette as he reminisced with fellow villagers in a language on the edge of extinction, one that partly traces its roots to the language Jesus Christ once spoke.
The 97-year-old Skordis is one of only 900 people in the world who speak Cypriot Maronite Arabic, or Sanna. Today, his village of Kormakitis is the last bastion of a language once spoken by tens of thousands of people across dozens of villages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only 900 speakers of the Sanna language remain. Now Cyprus&#39; Maronites are mounting a comeback</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-324559364/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-a-comeback-324559364/</guid>
      <description>KORMAKITIS, Cyprus &amp;ndash; Ash dangled precariously from Iosif Skordis&#39; cigarette as he reminisced with fellow villagers in a language on the edge of extinction, one that partly traces its roots to the language Jesus Christ once spoke.
The 97-year-old Skordis is one of only 900 people in the world who speak Cypriot Maronite Arabic, or Sanna. Today, his village of Kormakitis is the last bastion of a language once spoken by tens of thousands of people across dozens of villages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pete Doherty shows off his incredible weight loss  - after receiving shock &#39;wake-up call&#39; from health scare despite getting clean in 2019</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/pete-doherty-shows-off-his-incredible-weight-loss-after-receiving-shock-wakeup-call-from-health-scare-despite-getting-clean-in-2019-324436622/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/pete-doherty-shows-off-his-incredible-weight-loss-after-receiving-shock-wakeup-call-from-health-scare-despite-getting-clean-in-2019-324436622/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday
Kim Kardashian
Victoria Beckham
Harry Styles
Amanda Holden
Britain&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent
Privacy Policy
Saturday, May 24th 2025
5-Day Forecast
Advertisement
Full timeline of the hunt for missing girl Pheobe Bishop, 17, whose disappearance has gripped Australia
Brit woman, 21, rotting in Dubai hell hole jail without &amp;lsquo;a shower for a month&amp;rsquo; after being arrested for drugs charges just weeks after arriving for new job
James Martin rages at lawless London as yob smashes his car window after friends were mugged or had cars stolen in last two weeks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian millionaire blasted over &#39;Britain&#39;s most expensive council house&#39; forced to make drastic move a year after listing four-bed semi for £3.5m</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/russian-millionaire-blasted-over-britains-most-expensive-council-house-forced-to-make-drastic-move-a-year-after-listing-fourbed-semi-for-35m-324424114/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/russian-millionaire-blasted-over-britains-most-expensive-council-house-forced-to-make-drastic-move-a-year-after-listing-fourbed-semi-for-35m-324424114/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday
Latest Headlines
University Guide
Meghan Markle
Prince Harry
King Charles III
Privacy Policy
Saturday, May 24th 2025
5-Day Forecast
Advertisement
Full timeline of the hunt for missing girl Pheobe Bishop, 17, whose disappearance has gripped Australia
Gran, 48, faces eviction from her three-bed council house after spending £30k on garden makeover without planning permission
James Martin rages at lawless London as yob smashes his car window after friends were mugged or had cars stolen in last two weeks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish CCI announces new funding for ‘Restoring River Ravi Project’</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-cci-announces-new-funding-for-restoring-river-ravi-project-324294324/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-cci-announces-new-funding-for-restoring-river-ravi-project-324294324/</guid>
      <description>LAHORE: In a step towards water sustainability, Coca-Cola Içecek (CCI) Pakistan announced its new funding for Restoring River Ravi Project, during a stakeholder strategy session.
As part of its broader sustainability commitment, CCI Pakistan has pledged to achieve water neutrality by 2030. The Restoring River Ravi Project reflects this ambition, focusing on scalable and community-driven water replenishment initiatives in Lahore and Faisalabad.
“This project is not only about infrastructure—it is about long-term impact, collaboration, and responsibility,” said Sunay Sanl, General Manager CCI Pakistan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World News | Only 900 Speakers of the Sanna Language Remain. Now Cyprus&#39; Maronites Are Mounting Comeback</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/world-news-only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-comeback-324469196/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/world-news-only-900-speakers-of-the-sanna-language-remain-now-cyprus-maronites-are-mounting-comeback-324469196/</guid>
      <description>Kormakitis, May 24 (AP) Ash dangled precariously from Iosif Skordis&#39; cigarette as he reminisced with fellow villagers in a language on the edge of extinction, one that partly traces its roots to the language Jesus Christ once spoke. The 97-year-old Skordis is one of only 900 people in the world who speak Cypriot Maronite Arabic, or Sanna. Today, his village of Kormakitis is the last bastion of a language once spoken by tens of thousands of people across dozens of villages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘Turkish Cuisine Week’ celebrated with flavors, friendship in federal capital</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-cuisine-week-celebrated-with-flavors-friendship-in-federal-capital-324514122/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-cuisine-week-celebrated-with-flavors-friendship-in-federal-capital-324514122/</guid>
      <description>By Rehan Khan
ISLAMABAD, May 24 (APP): The Turkish Embassy in the federal capital opened its doors Saturday evening to celebrate the annual Turkish Cuisine Week, highlighting the rich culinary heritage of Turkiye and the deep-rooted brotherhood between Turkiye and Pakistan.
Hosted at the ambassador’s residence, the event brought together diplomats, government officials, media representatives, and distinguished guests for an evening of traditional Turkish flavors and cultural camaraderie.
Welcoming the guests, Ambassador of Turkiye to Pakistan, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey deploys more forces to help in al-Shabaab fight</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkey-deploys-more-forces-to-help-in-alshabaab-fight-324317738/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkey-deploys-more-forces-to-help-in-alshabaab-fight-324317738/</guid>
      <description>Hiiraan Online
Today from Hiiraan Online:
Somali Music
Google Plus
advertisements
Turkey deploys more forces to help in al-Shabaab fight
194 Shares FacebookFacebook messengerTwitterWhatsAppLinkedInTelegramEmail
Africa Defense Forum Friday May 23, 2025
Turkish marine forces stand guard aboard the Turkish Navy Ship F514 after it docked at the Mogadishu Sea Port, Mogadishu, Somalia, April 23, 2024. (Reuters Photo) Turkey is boosting its military presence in Somalia by deploying 500 troops specializing in counterterrorism and drone operations in response to recent territorial gains by al-Shabaab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blake Lively calls Ryan Reynolds &#39;most supportive husband&#39;... as Justin Baldoni lawsuit approaches 6th month mark</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/blake-lively-calls-ryan-reynolds-most-supportive-husband-as-justin-baldoni-lawsuit-approaches-6th-month-mark-323813080/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/blake-lively-calls-ryan-reynolds-most-supportive-husband-as-justin-baldoni-lawsuit-approaches-6th-month-mark-323813080/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday
Kim Kardashian
Victoria Beckham
Harry Styles
Amanda Holden
Britain&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent
Privacy Policy
Thursday, May 22nd 2025
5-Day Forecast
Advertisement
Unseen videos show Jay Slater bragging about £12k Rolex that he &amp;lsquo;took off some c***&amp;rsquo; in car with convicted drug dealer while &amp;lsquo;off his undies&amp;rsquo; hours before his death
Up to TEN feared dead after private plane crashes into San Diego neighborhood in huge fireball
How much is Chagos Islands surrender REALLY costing, Keir?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grieving family of mother whose heart was removed after she died in Turkey pay tribute to her - as they reveal there are &#39;a lot of unanswered questions&#39;</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/grieving-family-of-mother-whose-heart-was-removed-after-she-died-in-turkey-pay-tribute-to-her-as-they-reveal-there-are-a-lot-of-unanswered-questions-323861782/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/grieving-family-of-mother-whose-heart-was-removed-after-she-died-in-turkey-pay-tribute-to-her-as-they-reveal-there-are-a-lot-of-unanswered-questions-323861782/</guid>
      <description>The family of Beth Martin who died in mysterious circumstances on a family holiday in Turkey have paid a heartfelt tribute to her - as a fundraiser in her name nears £200,000.
The 28-year-old from Portsmouth set off on the dream trip with her husband Luke and their two young children Elouise, eight and Tommy, five, on Sunday April 27.
But after falling ill during the flight - something she initially blamed on food poisoning - her symptoms only worsened when they touched down in the holiday hotspot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Struggling &#39;Jose Mourinho player&#39; told to leave Man Utd - &#39;I feel really sorry for him&#39;</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/struggling-jose-mourinho-player-told-to-leave-man-utd-i-feel-really-sorry-for-him-323352680/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/struggling-jose-mourinho-player-told-to-leave-man-utd-i-feel-really-sorry-for-him-323352680/</guid>
      <description>Former Manchester United star Phil Jones believes Rasmus Hojlund would benefit from an Old Trafford exit. Hojlund, 22, has endured an arduous second campaign on the red side of Manchester, where he has failed to justify his price-tag. Since the Red Devils paid Atalanta £72million for his services in 2023 , the Dane has struggled for consistency in the United frontline. This season, he has only mustered ten goals and four assists in 50 appearances in all competitions, with nine of his goal contributions coming in the Europa League .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish Nobel Laureate Aziz Sancar receives Alisher Navoi International Prize - UzDaily.uz</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-nobel-laureate-aziz-sancar-receives-alisher-navoi-international-prize-uzdailyuz-323486362/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-nobel-laureate-aziz-sancar-receives-alisher-navoi-international-prize-uzdailyuz-323486362/</guid>
      <description>Tashkent, Uzbekistan (UzDaily.com) — As part of the informal summit of the Organization of Turkic States held in Budapest, the Alisher Navoi International Prize was awarded in recognition of outstanding contributions to the unity of the Turkic world.
This year’s recipient of the prestigious award is Aziz Sancar, an eminent Turkish biochemist, Nobel Prize laureate, and honorary doctor of the National University of Uzbekistan.
On this occasion, President of the Republic of Uzbekistan Shavkat Mirziyoyev extended heartfelt congratulations to Aziz Sancar, emphasizing that presenting such a distinguished award to a representative of the scientific community will serve as a powerful source of inspiration—particularly for the youth of the Turkic world striving for new achievements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India-Turkey Tensions Escalate After Ceasefire: Turkey’s Favor to Pakistan Triggers Indian Fury; Diplomats, Tourists, and Traders Lead Economic Boycott</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/indiaturkey-tensions-escalate-after-ceasefire-turkeys-favor-to-pakistan-triggers-indian-fury-diplomats-tourists-and-traders-lead-economic-boycott-323006758/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/indiaturkey-tensions-escalate-after-ceasefire-turkeys-favor-to-pakistan-triggers-indian-fury-diplomats-tourists-and-traders-lead-economic-boycott-323006758/</guid>
      <description>The fallout from the most recent India-Pakistan border conflict has spiraled far beyond the Line of Control. Following a fragile ceasefire after India’s bold Operation Sindoor, geopolitical tremors have rocked South Asia and the broader Islamic world. Central to this turbulence is the growing alliance between Pakistan and Turkey—a partnership now being openly challenged by India in an increasingly multipolar world.
In the latest diplomatic firestorm, India has responded with forceful economic and political retaliation after Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan expressed unwavering solidarity with Pakistan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre moment Turkey&#39;s Erdogan grabs Emmanuel Macron&#39;s finger at European summit and refuses to let go in &#39;power move&#39;</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/bizarre-moment-turkeys-erdogan-grabs-emmanuel-macrons-finger-at-european-summit-and-refuses-to-let-go-in-power-move-322831228/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/bizarre-moment-turkeys-erdogan-grabs-emmanuel-macrons-finger-at-european-summit-and-refuses-to-let-go-in-power-move-322831228/</guid>
      <description>Turkish president Recep Tayyip Erdogan could not let go of his French counterpart&amp;rsquo;s finger on Friday as the world leaders met at the European Political Community summit in Albania.
The awkward interaction between Emmanuel Macron and Erdogan was caught on camera, showing the politicians greeting each other with a handshake.
Erdogan, who is sat on a chair while Macron stands by his side, is shown grabbing onto the French president&amp;rsquo;s hand and shaking it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doha Hosts International Conference on Debate and Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/doha-hosts-international-conference-on-debate-and-dialogue-322990066/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/doha-hosts-international-conference-on-debate-and-dialogue-322990066/</guid>
      <description>Doha, May 19 (QNA) - QatarDebate, founded by Qatar Foundation, kicked off on Monday the second edition of the International Conference on Debate and Dialogue at Qatar National Convention Center.
The global event brings together over 800 intellectuals, academics, and a dynamic group of youth leaders, representing research, scientific, and cultural institutions from over 36 countries.
The opening ceremony was held in the presence of HE Minister of State at the Ministry of Foreign Affairs Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edo indigene urges Esan elders to honour Victor Osimhen with chieftaincy title</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/edo-indigene-urges-esan-elders-to-honour-victor-osimhen-with-chieftaincy-title-322869696/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/edo-indigene-urges-esan-elders-to-honour-victor-osimhen-with-chieftaincy-title-322869696/</guid>
      <description>Super Eagles striker Victor Osimhen has won both the Turkish Cup and the 2024/25 Turkish Super League titleThe 26-year-old set a new Galatasaray single-season record for most goals (36) by a foreign player, surpassing the previous record of 34 set by Brazilian legend Mario JardelFollowing his achievements, an Edo indigene has called on the Okhuesan community and the Esan Local Government Area to honour the striker with a chieftaincy title</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global seed sector gathers in Istanbul amid ongoing trade discussions that threaten seed availability and food security</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/global-seed-sector-gathers-in-istanbul-amid-ongoing-trade-discussions-that-threaten-seed-availability-and-food-security-322899616/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/global-seed-sector-gathers-in-istanbul-amid-ongoing-trade-discussions-that-threaten-seed-availability-and-food-security-322899616/</guid>
      <description>ISTANBUL, TURKEY, May 19, 2025 /EINPresswire.com/ &amp;ndash; Delegates from more than 70 countries have gathered in Istanbul for the largest seed industry event in the world, the World Seed Congress 2025, amid disruptions to global trading systems. The International Seed Federation (ISF), in collaboration with the Turkish National Organizing Committee, inaugurated the Congress, which brings together more than 1,600 seed industry professionals and seed sector insiders from around the world. Under the theme \&amp;ldquo;Discovering Bold Horizons,\&amp;rdquo; delegates at the Congress will address pressing challenges in plant breeding innovation, seed movement, food systems, and sustainable agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things to do May 23-29: Memorial Day events, Prairie Arts Festival, Gilberts Community Days and more</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/things-to-do-may-2329-memorial-day-events-prairie-arts-festival-gilberts-community-days-and-more-323775896/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/things-to-do-may-2329-memorial-day-events-prairie-arts-festival-gilberts-community-days-and-more-323775896/</guid>
      <description>Starts Before Friday
“Rock of Ages”: 7:30 p.m. Thursday through Saturday, May 22-24, and 2 p.m. Sunday, May 25, at the Metropolis Performing Arts Centre, 111 W. Campbell St., Arlington Heights. High-energy musical featuring the rock anthems and power ballads of Styx, Whitesnake, Pat Benatar, Poison and Twisted Sister. $20-$49. metropolisarts.com.
Friday, May 23
Turkish Festival: 10 a.m. to 10 p.m. Friday through Sunday, May 23-25, at the Donald E. Stephens Convention Center, 5555 N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish envoy visits Alkhidmat Foundation HQs</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-envoy-visits-alkhidmat-foundation-hqs-322697450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-envoy-visits-alkhidmat-foundation-hqs-322697450/</guid>
      <description>KARACHI: The Ambassador of the Republic of Türkiye to Pakistan, Dr Irfan Neziroglu, visited the national headquarters of Alkhidmat Foundation Pakistan in Lahore on Thursday.
He was warmly received by President Alkhidmat Foundation Dr Hafeez ur Rehman, Secretary General Syed Waqas Jafri, Vice Presidents Muhammad Abdus Shakoor, Syed Ihsanullah Waqas, Dr Mushtaq Mangat, and other senior officials.
During the visit, the Ambassador was given a detailed tour of the Alkhidmat Complex and briefed on the organisation’s ongoing humanitarian activities, both within Pakistan and internationally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boycott Turkey: Online Retailers Ajio, Myntra Suspend Sale Of Turkish Brands</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/boycott-turkey-online-retailers-ajio-myntra-suspend-sale-of-turkish-brands-322617756/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/boycott-turkey-online-retailers-ajio-myntra-suspend-sale-of-turkish-brands-322617756/</guid>
      <description>Indian ecommerce platforms such as Ajio and Myntra have removed Turkish apparel brands from their portals in response boycott calls triggered by Turkey’s support for Pakistan after India’s Operation Sindoor, launched to dismantle terror sites in Pakistan and Pakistan-occupied Kashmir (PoK) in aftermath of Pahalgam terror attck. Myntra has pulled Trendyol, a top-selling women’s fashion label in India, from its listings. Other Turkish brands like Koton, Mavi, and LC Waikiki have also disappeared from both Myntra and Ajio, either marked “out of stock” or removed altogether.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Caught On Cam: Turkish President Grips Emmanuel Macron&amp;#8217;s Finger For 13 Seconds, Gently Pats It During EPC Summit</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/caught-on-cam-turkish-president-grips-emmanuel-macron8217s-finger-for-13-seconds-gently-pats-it-during-epc-summit-322455538/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/caught-on-cam-turkish-president-grips-emmanuel-macron8217s-finger-for-13-seconds-gently-pats-it-during-epc-summit-322455538/</guid>
      <description>A peculiar moment between Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan and French President Emmanuel Macron during the European Political Community (EPC) summit in Albania has taken social media by storm. In the widely circulated video, Erdogan is seen gripping Macron’s hand and gently patting it — but what captured attention was how he unexpectedly held onto Macron’s index finger, even as the French leader attempted to pull away. Macron Appears Uncomfortable as Erdogan Holds His Finger The exchange began innocently with a handshake, but when Macron reached out with his other hand, Erdogan, while still seated, grasped Macron&amp;rsquo;s index finger and continued speaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan declares US lessening sanctions on Turkish defense division</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/erdogan-declares-us-lessening-sanctions-on-turkish-defense-division-322633980/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/erdogan-declares-us-lessening-sanctions-on-turkish-defense-division-322633980/</guid>
      <description>(MENAFN) The United States has begun relaxing sanctions on Türkiye’s defense industry and approved a significant arms sale, Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan announced over the weekend.The sanctions were originally imposed in 2020 under the Countering America’s Adversaries Through Sanctions Act (CAATSA), following Türkiye’s purchase of Russian-made S-400 air defense systems. Despite pressure from Washington, Ankara defended the deal, asserting its sovereign right to choose its defense partners.Speaking to journalists after attending the European Political Community summit in Albania, Erdogan stated, “We can now confidently say the CAATSA sanctions are being eased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Eases Sanctions on Turkish Defense Sector</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/us-eases-sanctions-on-turkish-defense-sector-322633968/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/us-eases-sanctions-on-turkish-defense-sector-322633968/</guid>
      <description>(MENAFN) Leader Recep Tayyip Erdogan has announced that the United States is easing sanctions on Türkiye’s defense industry and has approved a significant arms deal. In 2020, the US imposed restrictions on Ankara under the Countering America’s Adversaries Through Sanctions Act (CAATSA) following Türkiye’s acquisition of Russian S-400 air defense missile systems. Despite international pressure to abandon the deal with Moscow, Ankara upheld its stance, emphasizing its sovereign right to choose its own defense suppliers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US easing sanctions on Turkish defense sector – Erdogan</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/us-easing-sanctions-on-turkish-defense-sector-erdogan-322441310/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/us-easing-sanctions-on-turkish-defense-sector-erdogan-322441310/</guid>
      <description>The US is relaxing sanctions on Türkiye’s defense industry and has approved a major arms deal, President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has announced.
In 2020, Washington imposed restrictions on Ankara under the Countering America’s Adversaries Through Sanctions Act (CAATSA) in response to Türkiye’s purchase of Russia’s S-400 air defense missile system. Ankara repeatedly rejected calls to abandon the deal with Moscow, insisting on its sovereign right to choose its weapons suppliers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch: Turkey&#39;s Erdogan Grabs Emmanuel Macron&#39;s Finger, Doesn&#39;t Let Go</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/watch-turkeys-erdogan-grabs-emmanuel-macrons-finger-doesnt-let-go-322521636/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/watch-turkeys-erdogan-grabs-emmanuel-macrons-finger-doesnt-let-go-322521636/</guid>
      <description>French President Emmanuel Macron and his Turkish counterpart, Recep Tayyip Erdogan, shared an unusual interaction during the European Political Community (EPC) summit in Tirana that has sparked buzz online. In the now-viral footage, Macron can be seen reaching out for a handshake, patting Erdogan&amp;rsquo;s hands in a seemingly friendly gesture. However, instead of releasing Macron&amp;rsquo;s hand after the handshake, the Turkish President unexpectedly grasped the French leader&amp;rsquo;s finger and held on to it, while he appeared to stare off into the distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian boycott of Turkish goods condemned in Quetta</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/indian-boycott-of-turkish-goods-condemned-in-quetta-322197172/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/indian-boycott-of-turkish-goods-condemned-in-quetta-322197172/</guid>
      <description>QUETTA: The business community in Quetta on Friday condemned India’s boycott campaign against Turkish and Azerbaijani products and the cancellation of travel tickets to these countries by Indian citizens, calling it a reflection of frustration over support extended to Pakistan by Ankara and Baku during the recent conflict.
Quetta Chamber of Commerce and Industry President Haji Muhammad Ayub Miriani, Senior Vice-President Haji Akhtar Kakar, Vice-President Engineer Mir Wais Khan Kakar and former QCCI president and business leader Haji Ghulam Farooq Khilji said that in light of India’s decision, “it is the responsibility of the government of Pakistan and the business community to come forward and establish strong trade relations with the brotherly Islamic countries — Turkiye and Azerbaijan”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Officials across US government scramble to implement Trump’s surprise Syria announcement</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/officials-across-us-government-scramble-to-implement-trumps-surprise-syria-announcement-322538192/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/officials-across-us-government-scramble-to-implement-trumps-surprise-syria-announcement-322538192/</guid>
      <description>When President Donald Trump announced the lifting of US sanctions on Syria during his trip to the Middle East this week, it marked a major policy shift that could reshape the region and triggered a scramble across the US government to implement the decision, according to three sources familiar with the matter.
Trump administration officials had for months been carrying out quiet engagements to pave the way for sanctions relief and a potential high-level engagement with the former jihadist turned interim Syrian President Ahmed al-Sharaa, but the announcement sanctions would swiftly be removed altogether took some officials by surprise, according to the sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish, Saudi foreign ministers to co-chair 2nd Coordination Council session</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-saudi-foreign-ministers-to-cochair-2nd-coordination-council-session-322493624/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/turkish-saudi-foreign-ministers-to-cochair-2nd-coordination-council-session-322493624/</guid>
      <description>Turkish Foreign Minister Hakan Fidan and his Saudi counterpart Prince Faisal bin Farhan will co-chair the second session of their joint Coordination Council in Riyadh on Sunday, according to the Turkish Foreign Ministry, Anadolu reports.
Fidan will travel to Riyadh on Sunday for the second meeting of the Turkish-Saudi Coordination Council, his third visit to Saudi Arabia in the past year. His most recent trip was a working visit on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Remember your village people&#34;: Edo indigenes celebrate Victor Osimhen’s Turkish Cup win</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/remember-your-village-people-edo-indigenes-celebrate-victor-osimhens-turkish-cup-win-322130258/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/remember-your-village-people-edo-indigenes-celebrate-victor-osimhens-turkish-cup-win-322130258/</guid>
      <description>Super Eagles forward Victor Osimhen scored twice in the Turkish Cup final to break a 24-year record to help Galatasaray win The 26-year-old also set a new record with 35 goals in his debut season for the Turkish giants Edo indigenes have appealed to the 2023 CAF Player of the Year to remember his kinsmen in Edo state
Victor Osimhen powered Galatasaray to a 3-0 victory over Trabzonspor to lift the 2024 Turkish Cup on Wednesday night, May 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After Pakistan uses Turkish drones, Udaipur traders seek ban on Turkish marble imports</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/after-pakistan-uses-turkish-drones-udaipur-traders-seek-ban-on-turkish-marble-imports-322159784/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/after-pakistan-uses-turkish-drones-udaipur-traders-seek-ban-on-turkish-marble-imports-322159784/</guid>
      <description>Comments have to be in English, and in full sentences. They cannot be abusive or personal. Please abide by our community guidelines for posting your comments.
We have migrated to a new commenting platform. If you are already a registered user of TheHindu Businessline and logged in, you may continue to engage with our articles. If you do not have an account please register and login to post comments. Users can access their older comments by logging into their accounts on Vuukle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leeds issue statement after Ethan Ampadu’s son pictured in Galatasaray shirt</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/leeds-issue-statement-after-ethan-ampadus-son-pictured-in-galatasaray-shirt-322074566/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/leeds-issue-statement-after-ethan-ampadus-son-pictured-in-galatasaray-shirt-322074566/</guid>
      <description>Leeds have issued a statement distancing captain Ethan Ampadu from an online image of his son wearing a Galatasaray kit.
The club said the Wales defender was \&amp;ldquo;sensitive to\&amp;rdquo; the potential impact of the picture, which was posted by his former partner Saara Sa, on the families of supporters Christopher Loftus and Kevin Speight, who were murdered in Istanbul in 2000 on the eve of a UEFA Cup game against the Turkish side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low Expectations From Russia-Ukraine Talks In Turkey; Putin To Not Attend</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/low-expectations-from-russiaukraine-talks-in-turkey-putin-to-not-attend-321894342/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/low-expectations-from-russiaukraine-talks-in-turkey-putin-to-not-attend-321894342/</guid>
      <description>Delegations from Moscow and Kyiv will be in Istanbul Friday for what could be their first direct meeting on the conflict in Ukraine since 2022, but the absence of Russian President Vladimir Putin leaves little hope for progress in ending the war.US Secretary of State Marco Rubio downplayed expectations for the peace talks after Moscow sent a low-profile delegation and both sides traded insults ahead of the negotiations, initially slated for Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mother of Ethan Ampadu&#39;s son releases extraordinary response to Leeds statement</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/mother-of-ethan-ampadus-son-releases-extraordinary-response-to-leeds-statement-322046170/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/mother-of-ethan-ampadus-son-releases-extraordinary-response-to-leeds-statement-322046170/</guid>
      <description>The mother of Ethan Ampadu&amp;rsquo;s child has slammed Leeds United for &amp;lsquo;stating lies&amp;rsquo; in their statement about a picture of his son wearing a Galatasaray kit. There remains an angry feeling from Leeds fans towards the Turkish side. That is due to the murders of two Whites fans - Christopher Loftus and Kevin Speight - in Istanbul ahead of the 2000 UEFA Cup semi-final between the two sides. A picture has emerged in recent days of Ampadu&amp;rsquo;s son wearing a Gala shirt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President Ilham Aliyev meets Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan in Albania (VIDEO)</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/president-ilham-aliyev-meets-turkish-president-recep-tayyip-erdo%C4%9Fan-in-albania-video-321977672/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/president-ilham-aliyev-meets-turkish-president-recep-tayyip-erdo%C4%9Fan-in-albania-video-321977672/</guid>
      <description>TIRANA, Albania, May 16. President of the Republic of Azerbaijan, Ilham Aliyev, met with President of Türkiye Recep Tayyip Erdoğan in Albania as part of the 6th summit of the European Political Community (EPC), Trend reports.
Will be updated</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia And Ukraine To Meet In Istanbul, But Expectations Low</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/russia-and-ukraine-to-meet-in-istanbul-but-expectations-low-321854486/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/russia-and-ukraine-to-meet-in-istanbul-but-expectations-low-321854486/</guid>
      <description>Delegations from Moscow and Kyiv will be in Istanbul Friday for what could be their first direct meeting on the conflict in Ukraine since 2022, but the absence of Russian President Vladimir Putin leaves little hope for progress in ending the war.US Secretary of State Marco Rubio downplayed expectations for the peace talks after Moscow sent a low-profile delegation and both sides traded insults ahead of the negotiations, initially slated for Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia and Ukraine to meet in Istanbul, but expectations low</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/russia-and-ukraine-to-meet-in-istanbul-but-expectations-low-321852024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/russia-and-ukraine-to-meet-in-istanbul-but-expectations-low-321852024/</guid>
      <description>Delegations from Moscow and Kyiv will be in Istanbul on Friday for what could be their first direct meeting on the conflict in Ukraine since 2022, but the absence of Russian President Vladimir Putin leaves little hope for progress in ending the war.US Secretary of State Marco Rubio downplayed expectations for the peace talks after Moscow sent a low-profile delegation and both sides traded insults ahead of the negotiations, initially slated for Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top online retailers like Ajio, Reliance halt sale of Turkish brands</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/top-online-retailers-like-ajio-reliance-halt-sale-of-turkish-brands-322118532/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/top-online-retailers-like-ajio-reliance-halt-sale-of-turkish-brands-322118532/</guid>
      <description>Myntra and Reliance-owned Ajio have stopped selling Turkish apparel brands on their portals amid growing boycott calls since Turkey backed Pakistan during the recent military conflict between India and Pakistan. Myntra has temporarily halted sales of all Turkish brands including Trendyol, owned by internet giant Alibaba, for which it has an exclusive right to market in India, according to two industry executives privy to the development. Reliance, too, has suspended all of its Turkish apparel brands portfolio such as Koton, LC Waikiki and Mavi sold on its online platform Ajio, with all their products showing out of stock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Tweets Threaten Thrones: The Curious Case of Ekrem İmamoğlu and the Price of Free Speech</title>
      <link>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/when-tweets-threaten-thrones-the-curious-case-of-ekrem-imamo%C4%9Flu-and-the-price-of-free-speech-322130456/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://berkdenk.github.io/Hugo_NewsAPI/posts/when-tweets-threaten-thrones-the-curious-case-of-ekrem-imamo%C4%9Flu-and-the-price-of-free-speech-322130456/</guid>
      <description>In an age where cat videos, motivational quotes, and political revolutions all coexist on the same timeline, it takes true genius to look at a politician’s Twitter account and exclaim, “This is the real threat to public order!” And yet, here we are – welcoming the news that Turkish authorities have taken the bold, courageous, and oh-so-democratically spirited step of blocking access to Istanbul Mayor Ekrem İmamoğlu’s X (formerly Twitter) account within Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
