<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on My News Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on My News Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Under the Visionary Leadership of the Prime Minister, India is making Premium Global Education Available at an Affordable Cost: Shri Dharmendra Pradhan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/under-the-visionary-leadership-of-the-prime-minister-india-is-making-premium-global-education-available-at-an-affordable-cost-shri-dharmendra-pradhan-331376904/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/under-the-visionary-leadership-of-the-prime-minister-india-is-making-premium-global-education-available-at-an-affordable-cost-shri-dharmendra-pradhan-331376904/</guid>
      <description>Ministry of Education
Under the Visionary Leadership of the Prime Minister, India is making Premium Global Education Available at an Affordable Cost: Shri Dharmendra Pradhan
In a Major Initiative Towards Fulfilling NEP 2020 Vision, Letter of Intents (LOIs) Issued to Five Foreign Universities - University of York, University of Aberdeen, University of Western Australia, Illinois Institute of Technology, and Instituto Europeo Di Design (IED), Italy to set-up Campuses in Mumbai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sustaining global cooperation in a fragmenting world</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sustaining-global-cooperation-in-a-fragmenting-world-330213182/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sustaining-global-cooperation-in-a-fragmenting-world-330213182/</guid>
      <description>Speech by Christine Lagarde, President of the ECB, at the People’s Bank of China in Beijing
Beijing, 11 June 2025
It is a pleasure to be back here in Beijing.
Some years ago, I spoke about how a changing world was creating a new global map of economic relations.[1]
Maps have always reflected the society in which they are produced. But in rare instances, they can also capture historical moments when two societies meet at the crossroads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shri Dharmendra Pradhan chairs Global Young Scientists Conference and Annual General Meeting of the Global Young Academy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shri-dharmendra-pradhan-chairs-global-young-scientists-conference-and-annual-general-meeting-of-the-global-young-academy-329913660/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shri-dharmendra-pradhan-chairs-global-young-scientists-conference-and-annual-general-meeting-of-the-global-young-academy-329913660/</guid>
      <description>Ministry of Education
Shri Dharmendra Pradhan chairs Global Young Scientists Conference and Annual General Meeting of the Global Young Academy
India believes in science that is empathetic, ethical, and equitable - Shri Dharmendra Pradhan
Scientists must collaborate and co-create with a sense of purpose and empathy to realise the vision of Viksit Bharat and advance human-centric development - Shri Dharmendra Pradhan
10 JUN 2025 2:38PM by PIB Delhi
Union Minister for Education, Shri Dharmendra Pradhan, today chaired the Global Young Scientists Conference and Annual General Meeting of the Global Young Academy at IIT Hyderabad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>J Balvin, Doja Cat and Tems to headline the inaugural FIFA Club World Cup™ Final Halftime Show, produced by Global Citizen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/j-balvin-doja-cat-and-tems-to-headline-the-inaugural-fifa-club-world-cup-final-halftime-show-produced-by-global-citizen-329988844/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/j-balvin-doja-cat-and-tems-to-headline-the-inaugural-fifa-club-world-cup-final-halftime-show-produced-by-global-citizen-329988844/</guid>
      <description>FIFA Club World Cup 2025™ final set to achieve the largest worldwide reach ever for a global club tournament Today, FIFA and Global Citizen announced that J Balvin, Doja Cat and Tems will headline the inaugural FIFA Club World Cup™️ Halftime Show on Sunday, 13 July 2025, firing up the MetLife Stadium in New York New Jersey.
The show will be broadcast live and for free all over the world on DAZN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scholars&#39; Perspectives: &#39;For Good Purposes&#39; Serves As The Greatest Common Denominator Of Global Technology Development, Says Member Of UN Advisory Body On AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/scholars-perspectives-for-good-purposes-serves-as-the-greatest-common-denominator-of-global-technology-development-says-member-of-un-advisory-body-on-ai-328176994/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/scholars-perspectives-for-good-purposes-serves-as-the-greatest-common-denominator-of-global-technology-development-says-member-of-un-advisory-body-on-ai-328176994/</guid>
      <description>BEIJING, June 4, 2025 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; May 30, 2025 marks the ninth National Science and Technology Workers Day. In the early morning of the previous day, Tianwen-2, the country&amp;rsquo;s first asteroid probe and sampling mission, soared into the sky, carrying with it humanity&amp;rsquo;s aspirations for the stars and the universe.
The nation will thrive when science and technology develops, and the country will be strong when science and technology becomes advanced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Global Brand: Practical branding strategies for international growth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-a-global-brand-practical-branding-strategies-for-international-growth-325873312/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-a-global-brand-practical-branding-strategies-for-international-growth-325873312/</guid>
      <description>I attended the recent conference on Women in Trade and Investment organised by the Women of Africa Network (WOAN) and Ecobank Ghana in collaboration with the AfCTFA Secretariat, where I spoke on \&amp;ldquo;Building a Global Brand: Practical Branding Strategies for International Growth.\&amp;rdquo; Given the importance of this topic, not only to women entrepreneurs but to Ghanaian businesses in general, I would like to share my thoughts here. So here we go…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BDMT GLOBAL PARTNERS WITH MEDEVICE BOSTON TO HELP U.S. MEDTECH LEADERS HARNESS KOREA’S CUTTING-EDGE TECHNOLOGY</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bdmt-global-partners-with-medevice-boston-to-help-us-medtech-leaders-harness-koreas-cuttingedge-technology-325545728/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bdmt-global-partners-with-medevice-boston-to-help-us-medtech-leaders-harness-koreas-cuttingedge-technology-325545728/</guid>
      <description>BOSTON, MA, UNITED STATES, May 27, 2025 /EINPresswire.com/ &amp;ndash; BDMT Global, an award-winning, Boston-based group of global business development and marketing experts with a turnkey market expansion expertise for global industry innovatorsâannounced the BDMT Global + MEDevice Boston Innovator Summit 2025, a curated program designed to drive collaborations between global MedTech innovators and U.S. ecosystem players to solve critical challenges. The Innovator Summit, hosted in partnership with MEDevice Boston on September 30 â October 1, marks the next pillar of BDMT Globalâs DAC Global Bridge Series to provide a one-stop destination for collaboration opportunities between companies, which will be expanding to additional leading trade shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global South’s video media plays crucial role in promoting development: new report</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/global-souths-video-media-plays-crucial-role-in-promoting-development-new-report-324933604/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/global-souths-video-media-plays-crucial-role-in-promoting-development-new-report-324933604/</guid>
      <description>A GLOBAL South Media Exchange initiative was launched in Beijing, alongside the release of the “2024 Report on Development of Video Media in the Global South”, ushering in a new era of collaboration between China and other members of the Global South region to enhance their online media platforms to tell their stories to the world.
The launching ceremony was held on Friday 23 May at the CCTV+ headquarters.
Media representatives from the Asia, Pacific and Caribbean regions as well as Iran and Turkey, attending a media exchange program hosted by the China International Press and Communication Center (CIPCC) for international journalists, participated in the program alongside officials and experts from the Chinese media industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Times: Ningbo-Zhoushan Port’s global connectivity seen from a small button controlling bridge crane</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/global-times-ningbozhoushan-ports-global-connectivity-seen-from-a-small-button-controlling-bridge-crane-324931554/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/global-times-ningbozhoushan-ports-global-connectivity-seen-from-a-small-button-controlling-bridge-crane-324931554/</guid>
      <description>BEIJING, May 26, 2025 /PRNewswire/ — When Zhu Shijie started working at the Chuanshan port area of Ningbo-Zhoushan Port in East China’s Zhejiang Province in 1999 as a bridge crane operator loading and unloading containers onto or from ships, the port’s annual handling of 500,000 containers was celebrated with a ceremony. In 2025, the veteran crane operator, said he hopes he could be the one to press the button that picks up this year’s 38 millionth container milestone for Ningbo Zhoushan Port Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFS Global acquires majority stake in CiX Citizen Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfs-global-acquires-majority-stake-in-cix-citizen-experience-323139662/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfs-global-acquires-majority-stake-in-cix-citizen-experience-323139662/</guid>
      <description>VFS Global, the global leader in trusted technology services, empowering secure global mobility for governments and citizens, has completed the acquisition of a majority stake in CiX Citizen Experience, a leading provider of digital and physical citizen services based in Brazil.
This strategic acquisition marks a pivotal step in VFS Global’s expansion journeyas it continues to broaden its capabilities and deepen its impact in the public service delivery space. With nearly two decades of pioneering innovation in citizen services, CiX has established a strong presence in Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VFS Global acquires majority stake in CiX Citizen Experience to create a centre of excellence and promote Brazilian knowhow in Public Service abroad</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfs-global-acquires-majority-stake-in-cix-citizen-experience-to-create-a-centre-of-excellence-and-promote-brazilian-knowhow-in-public-service-abroad-323081570/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vfs-global-acquires-majority-stake-in-cix-citizen-experience-to-create-a-centre-of-excellence-and-promote-brazilian-knowhow-in-public-service-abroad-323081570/</guid>
      <description>Supercharged Growth: VFS Global’s partnership will accelerate CiX’s expansion across key makets in Africa
Global Powerhouse: With VFS Global’s capital, technology, talent and scale, CiX Citizen Experience will bring new products and technology to the global marketplace.
Quality of Life Commitment: Both companies are dedicated to innovative solutions, including the use of AI, that improve citizens’ quality of life
. Local Impact with Wider Reach: Collaboration to modernise services for citizens of Brazil by creating a centre of excellence that stands as a global example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billboard’s 2025 Global Power Players Revealed</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/billboards-2025-global-power-playersrevealed-322950190/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/billboards-2025-global-power-playersrevealed-322950190/</guid>
      <description>Recorded music is a small but mighty sector” of the world’s business, IFPI CEO Victoria Oakley said as she introduced the organizations’s annual report in March. “It’s a part of the global economy that really matters. Above all, it’s a powerful example of human artistry and connectivity.”
Oakley quantified the impact of that artistry with a report full of good news — mostly. The recorded-music business worldwide grew for the 10th consecutive year, despite concerns raised by generative artificial intelligence (AI) using copyright-protected music to train its systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qatar Economic Forum Maps Out the Next Chapter in Global Economic Growth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/qatar-economic-forum-maps-out-the-next-chapter-in-global-economic-growth-322805036/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/qatar-economic-forum-maps-out-the-next-chapter-in-global-economic-growth-322805036/</guid>
      <description>Doha, May 19 (QNA) - Under the theme &amp;lsquo;The Road to 2030: Transforming the Global Economy,&amp;rsquo; the fifth edition of the Qatar Economic Forum, Powered by Bloomberg, will kick off Tuesday in Doha in collaboration with Media City Qatar.
The Forum will take place from May 20-22 and will bring together a distinguished group of global leaders and influential CEOs to discuss key issues that are reshaping the global economic landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Times: White paper highlights China&#39;s proactive, steadfast practice of GSI, stresses country&#39;s contribution to global security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/global-times-white-paper-highlights-chinas-proactive-steadfast-practice-of-gsi-stresses-countrys-contribution-to-global-security-321876896/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/global-times-white-paper-highlights-chinas-proactive-steadfast-practice-of-gsi-stresses-countrys-contribution-to-global-security-321876896/</guid>
      <description>BEIJING, May 15, 2025 /PRNewswire/ &amp;ndash; China&amp;rsquo;s State Council Information Office on Monday released its first white paper on the country&amp;rsquo;s national security in the new era. The white paper systematically elaborates on the theoretical system of China&amp;rsquo;s holistic approach to national security for the first time.
According to the white paper, China&amp;rsquo;s holistic approach to national security is the first major strategic thinking established as the guiding principle for national security efforts since the founding of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azerbaijan&#39;s strategic role in rise of Global South: Bridge between worlds</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/azerbaijans-strategic-role-in-rise-of-global-south-bridge-between-worlds-321503022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/azerbaijans-strategic-role-in-rise-of-global-south-bridge-between-worlds-321503022/</guid>
      <description>In contemporary geopolitical discourse, the terms Global South and Global North do not refer strictly to geographic hemispheres but to divisions in socio-economic development, political influence, and historical trajectories. The Global North typically includes developed nations - primarily in Western Europe, North America, and parts of East Asia - with advanced economies, technological infrastructure, and significant global influence. In contrast, the Global South encompasses a diverse group of nations across Africa, Latin America, Asia, and parts of Eastern Europe that have historically been marginalised in global decision-making but are now asserting increasing agency and influence on the world stage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
